Vasyl Kish Web Developer PHP & JavaScript

www.linkedin.com/in/vasya-kish-bb4161138/ https://github.com/V-Kish http://the-kish.zzz.com.ua/

+380 68 422 01 87 skype: vasya.kish94

gmail: vasya.kish94@gmail.com

Recent Location: Lviv



Skills

Education

Junior Specialist

Software Engineering,

Uzhgorod Technical College

Bachelor

Software Engineering, Uzhgorod National University

Communication

Ukrainian	Native language
Russian	Fluent
English	Pre-Intermediate
Slovakian	Basic
Czech	Basic

Tools & programming language

Photoshop, HTML 5, CSS 3, Gulp, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, GIT, OOP, MVC, Ajax & JSON

Work history

June 2016 — October 2017

(Uzhgorod, Ukraine)

Freelance Web Developer.

Creating personal projects for small business and personal customers.

May 2018 — August 2018

(Uzhgorod, Ukraine)

Front-End Developer

Thinkmobiles.

Working on internal projects and own company products.

https://thinkmobiles.com/

September 2018 — December

2018 (Brno, Czechia)

NAVERTICA Inc.
Software company.

http://www.navertica.com/

About

Since 2015 I have been working in freelance with different orders, from personal sites to online stores.

In 2017 won the contests «Ukrainian Design Awards», «One Page Love», «CSS Winner», and «UpLabs Best of the Day».

In 2018 won the contest «Indigo Design Awwards»